Inventory of the Thomas Byrne Edsall papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Monica Lewinsky and Clinton (Box 251)
  - Folder 3 of 3, magazines and reports, 1981-2003 (Box-folder 251: 2)
  - Folder 2 of 3, articles and notes, 1992-2004 (Box-folder 252: 1)
- Miscellany, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 253: 1-5)
  Fragments of writings in progress; articles including one, "Silent Flight," by Alexandra Edsall; clippings; magazine; newsletter; notes; and poems
- Incremental Materials (Box 254-266)
- 2015 Incremental Materials, 2006-2014 (Box 267)
  - Bradlee, Ben, undated (Box-folder 267: 1)
  - Columbia University School Commencement Program, 2007 (Box-folder 267: 2)
  - Correspondence, 2007-2014 (Box-folder 267: 3)
  - Course proposal, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 4)
  - The Huffington Post materials, 2007 (Box-folder 267: 5)
  - Folder labeled "ideas", 2006 (Box-folder 267: 6)
  - Folder labeled "jokes", undated (Box-folder 267: 7)
  - Journal proposal, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 8)
  - Lemann, Nicholas, 2007 (Box-folder 267: 9)
  - Macdonald, Michael C.D., 2006 (Box-folder 267: 10)
  - Master's Thesis advisor's note, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 11)
  - Meeting with Jane H. Furse and John Friedman notes, 2007 (Box-folder 267: 12)
  - National Journal, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 13)
  - The New Republic Letter of Agreement, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 14)
  - The New York Times materials, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 267: 15)
  - The Politics of Scarcity manuscript with notes, 2011 (Box-folder 267: 16-18)
  - Russell Sage Foundation application, 9/30/2013 (Box-folder 267: 19)
    Includes the curriculum vitae of Thomas B. Edsall
  - Speaking engagements, 2014 (Box-folder 267: 20)
  - Syllabi, 2006-2010 (Box-folder 267: 21)
  - Thank you cards, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 267: 22)
  - Material regarding the "Top 50 Journalists of 2009", 2010 (Box-folder 267: 23)
  - Wald, Richard, 2006 (Box-folder 267: 24)
  - Two CD-Rs labeled "Jeff Jones NY Daily News Strike", one CD-R labeled "French Dossier 12/19/2013", and one DVD labeled "Polarization: a Dangerously Divided America", 2012-2013 (Box-folder 267: 25)